<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CamStorr Partner</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_account">Account</string>
    <string name="app_version">1.0.0</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">A Terms and Conditions agreement acts as legal contracts between you
        (the company) who has the website or mobile app, and the store who accesses your website/app.
        Having a Terms and Conditions agreement is completely optional. No laws require you to have one.
        Not even the super-strict and wide-reaching General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
        Your Terms and Conditions agreement will be uniquely yours. While some clauses are standard and
        commonly seen in pretty much every Terms and Conditions agreement, it\'s up to you to set the
        rules and guidelines that the store must agree to.  You can think of your Terms and Conditions
        agreement as the legal agreement where you maintain your rights to exclude users from your app in
        the event that they abuse your app, where you maintain your legal rights against potential app abusers,
        and so on.  Terms and Conditions agreements are also known as Terms of Service or Terms of Use agreements.
        These terms are interchangeable, practically speaking.  Check out our Terms and Conditions FAQ for
        more helpful insight into these important agreements.</string>
    <string name="new_complaint_fab">New Complaint</string>
    <string name="empty_complaints_info">No previous complaints</string>
    <string name="random_text_for_testing">"This is some random text for testing again and again This is some random text for testing again and again This is some random text for testing again and again This is some random text for testing again and again "</string>
    <string-array name="complaints_list">
        <item>Payment Related</item>
        <item>QR scanning Related</item>
        <item>Store Related</item>
        <item>Login Related</item>
        <item>Bug in app</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brands_list_default">
        <item>Any</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="camera_types_list_default">
        <item>Any</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="hard_disk_list_default">
        <item>Any</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="camera_sub_category">
        <item>Dome Shaped</item>
        <item>Bullet</item>
        <item>Thermal</item>
        <item>PTZ</item>
        <item>Day Night</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="accessory_sub_category">
        <item>Hard Disk</item>
        <item>Monitor</item>
        <item>Wires</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gst_list">
        <item>10%</item>
        <item>12%</item>
        <item>18%</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sales_spinner_list">
        <item>Today\'s Sales</item>
        <item>Last 7 days</item>
        <item>Last 30 days</item>
        <item>Total Sales</item>
        <item>Custom Date</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>